North Pacific Program, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Records UA189
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- John Perry records, 1980 -- 2018; UA189.003; 3.1 Linear Feet
  - Fletcher and North Pacific Program newsletters, 1989 -- 1992; UA189.003.010.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence Korea Summer Seminar, 1991; UA189.003.010.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Fletcher-Seoul Summer Seminal proposal and budget, 1991; UA189.003.010.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Korea Summer Seminar, 1991; UA189.003.010.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Proposal for trilateral conference, 1986 -- 1989; UA189.003.010.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Intersect, circa 1990s; UA189.003.010.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Sungsan Group Inc., 1986 -- 1991; UA189.003.010.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Professor John C. Perry NPP, 1996; UA189.003.011.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - NPP Mexico Summer Seminar, 1995; UA189.003.011.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - North Pacific Program Sanwa Lecture Series, 1989 -- 1992; UA189.003.011.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
  - Fletcher-Hokkaido Seminar, 1983 -- 1991; UA189.003.011.00004; 3 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - End of Hokkaido Program, 1990 -- 1991; UA189.003.011.00005; 3 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 9-11)
  - Korea, 1999; UA189.003.011.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - North Pacific Summer Seminar, 1995 -- 1996; UA189.003.011.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Sasakawa Young Leaders Fellowship, 1984 -- 1995; UA189.003.011.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - North Pacific Region Advanced Research Center, 1987 -- 2002; UA189.003.011.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - North Pacific advisory council, 1984 -- 1988; UA189.003.011.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Saehan Media Corp, 1987 -- 1996; UA189.003.011.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mis expenses, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Rockefeller bros fund, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Sanwa Lecture Series, 1987 -- 1993; UA189.003.011.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Professor Rhoads Murphey, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 21)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - John J Stephan's visit to Fletcher, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Stephan's CV, 1989; UA189.003.011.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Thank you ltrs on Sanwa Report, 1988; UA189.003.011.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - North Pacific Program correspondence and review, 1993 -- 2018; UA189.003.011.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Sanwa Bank Ltd, 1990 -- 1995; UA189.003.011.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Kapalua, 1986; UA189.003.011.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Vladivostok, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.003.011.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Hokkaido program reports, 1985; UA189.003.011.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - NPP summer applications, circa 1980s -- 1990s; UA189.003.011.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - US - Japan Foundation, 1981 -- 1983; UA189.003.011.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - NIRA, 1986 -- 1988; UA189.003.011.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Rissho Kosei-Kai, 1986 -- 1992; UA189.003.011.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Proposal to Samsung, 1982 -- 1983; UA189.003.011.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Sanwa research fellow, 1986 -- 1995; UA189.003.011.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Korea Foundation, 1994 -- 1998; UA189.003.011.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Correspondences, 1986 -- 1988; UA189.003.011.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Sasakawa, 1983 -- 1984; UA189.003.011.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Fletcher School correspondence, 2006 -- 2018; UA189.003.011.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Sanwa lecture series booklets, 1988 -- 1993; UA189.003.011.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - North Pacific Program summer seminar booklets, 1990 -- 1996; UA189.003.011.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - NPP programs, 1986 -- 1997; UA189.003.011.00036; 3 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Latest faxes Hokkaido, 1990; UA189.003.011.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Hokkaido schedules, memo, meetings, 1990; UA189.003.011.00038; 2 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 44-45)
  - Fletcher Hokkaido logistics, 1990; UA189.003.011.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Hokkaido student resumes, 1990; UA189.003.011.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Fletcher Hokkaido participants, 1989; UA189.003.011.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Selection committee, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Acceptances Hokkaido Vladivostok, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.011.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Visiting Soviet info, 1989 -- 1991; UA189.003.011.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Amabassador Pickering lecture/ Valery I Denisov lecture, 1994; UA189.003.012.00001; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 1)
  - Moscow Seminar - Katya Egorava lecture (II + III), 1994; UA189.003.012.00002; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 2)
  - Minister Togo lecture / Katya Egorova lecture (I of III), 1994; UA189.003.012.00003; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 3)
  - Moscow North Pacific Seminar Boris Makarenko lecture (III), 1994; UA189.003.012.00004; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 4)
  - Moscow North Pacific Seminar Boris Makarenko lecture (I + II), 1994; UA189.003.012.00005; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 5)
  - Moscow North Pacific Seminar wrap-up session/ Quaker meeting, 1994; UA189.003.012.00006; 1 Cassettes (Box 12, Object 6)
  - Sevilla Seminar 2001, UA189.003.013.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - NPP Mexico Summer Seminar, 1995; UA189.003.013.00002; 2 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Zhonghua Renmin Gongheguo Ditu map, circa 1980s -- 2000s; UA189.003.013.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Shijie Ditu map, circa 1980s -- 2000s; UA189.003.013.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1987 -- 2000; UA189.003.014.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hokkaido letter to all non Fletcher students, 1989; UA189.003.014.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hokkaid tent. Schedule, 1989; UA189.003.014.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - University of Tokyo, 1987 -- 1995; UA189.003.014.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - NPP Tokyo Kanazawa, 1993; UA189.003.014.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Minutes to meetings Japan, 1989; UA189.003.014.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hokkaido student responsibilities, 1989; UA189.003.014.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Matsue Correspondence, 1988; UA189.003.014.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - NPI proposals and info, 1989 -- 1990; UA189.003.014.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Fletcher Hokkaido booklet, 1989; UA189.003.014.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Fletcher board of visitors, 1985 -- 1988; UA189.003.014.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Vladivostok lecture, 1990; UA189.003.014.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Alla Solovyeva, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.003.014.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - NPP Moscow, 1994; UA189.003.014.00014; 2 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - Executive committee minutes, 1988 -- 1989; UA189.003.014.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - FH correspondence, 1987; UA189.003.015.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Student acceptance letters, 1987; UA189.003.015.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Japan and Korea, 1996; UA189.003.015.00003; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Sakhalin USSR, 1992; UA189.003.015.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989; UA189.003.015.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Hokkaido program, 1985; UA189.003.015.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Projects and reports, 1990 -- 1992; UA189.003.015.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Development, 1984; UA189.003.015.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Fletcher North Pacific Institute, 1989 -- 1991; UA189.003.015.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Annual faculty self evaluation, 1996 -- 1998; UA189.003.015.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Sasakawa, 1995 -- 1999; UA189.003.015.00011; 2 Folder(s) (Box 15, Folder 12-13)